That if I say that you give me a point of ₹3
and I give you a point of ₹10, how did you like it, then it is
very interesting,
yes friends, it refers to a
hospital insurance policy
which is very important for you, in which case you get a lot of
benefits, if you
ever get hospitalized, even if it is
in a government hospital,
and here you do
n't even need to show the hospital bill, let's
now talk about this policy,
some tips, how can you buy the point,
what are the conditions, how can you click, in
this condition you will not get the money, I will
tell you everything in this video, so
let's quickly request, if you
like the video, then don't forget to like the video, don't
forget to subscribe to our channel, my name is
Vidhan, you will see that the website can do that,
secondly, before telling you the test of this policy, let me
talk to you about the purpose of gas, so
if by chance any
person has to sleep in the hospital, then
in that condition only the oil bill will be charged  It cannot be
treated only and only, does money
ever hurt? Apart from this, if any
earning member gets hospitalized
for 10-15 days, then his income also
stops for a few days, so to
help you in that condition,
this policy was launched like on phone, if you are
admitted for more than 48 hours, then
now you will use this policy, you get
four different policies,
according to that you will get money per day
and to claim this point
you do not need any hostel at all, whether
you are admitted in a private hospital
or a government hospital,
if you are hospitalized for
more than 48 hours, then you will get the money here,
here you get to see four different policies, the
starting
price of Pulsar is only ₹100 and the
price of Hotspot is ₹70, if you
take an audition of ₹70, then you will get a benefit of up
to ₹5000 there.  You will get the benefit if
your password is ever hospitalized
in that condition and if you live in normal rate
then you will get ₹5 but if you
live in ID then in that condition
you will get money up to ₹10 for 250 hours, the maximum amount
of money is ₹
25000, yes friends and you will have to
take this only one time for ₹1270,
you will not have to pay any extra and
after 1 year if you want to renew it then
you can do that too because of the including quality
that if you are an Australian then
in that condition also you can
get that much money, apart from this if you
want to buy this policy then your age should be
between 18 to 65 years, then
you can buy this policy,
talk about the waiting period here, if
you have to
go in the waiting period then if
something happens to you in the meantime then you will
not get any benefit in that condition but if  If there's a
chance an accident happens, there's no
waiting period.
If you're admitted immediately,
you can still
get all these benefits. This comes
from Lamba General Insurance Company,
so you do
n't have to worry at all because it's a very
large insurance company. Friends,
I'm showing you on my mobile screen
how easily you can secure this policy.
To buy the policy, you'll need to go to the "Applications" section on your phone. You'll find the "
Manik" option below.
You'll find the "Hospital Surajpol" option inside it.
If you click on the "Sense" option for this hospital,
you'll see four different
options available. You
can buy the policy based on your recruitment needs. I've also listed a "Question" section above
where you can click and
see the answers to all your questions. You'll find the answer to
whatever question you have here.
However, I'll explain everything to you later
in the video.  I will tell
you about such insurance, so
keep watching this video and if you
click here, you can see that whatever
policy you want to buy, if you click here now, then
inside it you can see that here
you get the benefits option
where you can see the details about the policy,
what facilities you get here,
like in this you will get
₹5000, if you are admitted in ICU then you will get
rs.10000, all these facilities have been
mentioned here and buying the policy
is very simple, just here you have to
click on PIN, after giving your email ID and date of
birth, you can buy a policy,
you can
pay here through any medium like debit card, you
can use whatever you want,
you will get the details on your email ID,
after making the payment, friends, if you feel that
you have gained some knowledge from this video, then do
not forget to like this video and yes, do not
forget to subscribe to this policy.
If you feel that
you do not need to take this policy, then
in that condition you
can get a refund of the full amount. Here you can
also see this field being quite popular.
Friends, whatever insurance policies there are,
some of them have to be done.
In some conditions, you do not get any benefits. So,
by transferring some of this simple and easy policy, friends, I
would like to tell you one thing here that you do
not get any money for the first 24 hours. As if
you enroll for seven days
in voice mail, then you will get the money for six
days. You will not get any money for the first 24 hours.
Apart from this,
suppose you get the money for six days, out of which
you spend three days in channel bag
and the remaining three days in cash, then for three days
you will get the notification for the first three days and for the remaining three days you will get
double the money. So, this also becomes
clear to you here. So
friends, now let's talk about the
most important thing of the feeder, the
policy of traffic, you can make a policy
claim.  You will have to call on this number which is a toll
free number, you can get it here,
you will have to contact on this toll free number
or you can also contact for milk
and polish, its conical, you do
not need to give many documents, in whichever hospital you are admitted,
you will have to give a photo copy of the discussion with the person with whom you meet us,
as the company says that the
work will be done with that and if the money is not transferred then it will be
transferred to your bank account,
when you call for polish, at that time whichever
bank account number you give, your money will be transferred to that place, the
company says that there is another
insurance plan on the phone, for this, Paytm,
Flipkart, Power Insurance Policy,
we have already made videos, I will
click on the i button above, go from there and
definitely watch it once, look at all the plans carefully,
compare them, then
use it, friends, including the cylinder,
in today's video I hope that you have got
full knowledge and information from this video,
if you like the video then do
not forget to like the video, if you want any right question
You can ask by commenting,
I will reply to your comment
here. Friends, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then with folded hands I
request you to definitely
subscribe to the channel. You will get to see its mode of
information video in future also, so
let's meet
about this, till then goodbye, thank you so much,
thank you very much for watching the video.